positivepromotions.com 2019-08-27

# Privacy Policy | Positive Promotions

Positive Promotions, Inc. ("Company") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy tells you about the personal and other information that we gather from you and what we do with that information. By using this Website you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy and consent to the collection and use of your information by Company as described below. Company reserves the right, at its discretion, to make changes to this policy at any time.

* * *

**The Information We Collect And How We Use It**

Company wants to provide you with an efficient, easy-to-use, and customized service. For this reason, we collect some personal information from you, but we try to keep the information that we collect to an absolute minimum. When you purchase a product from Company, you provide such personal information as: (i) your name; (ii) billing address; (iii) e-mail address; (iv) phone numbers; and (vi) credit card account number. This allows us to fulfill your order and provide you with the best possible customer service. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. 

Company may use the information it collects to tailor your experience at Company's site. Company may also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help it develop the design and layout of the site. And, we may use the information for such things as notifying you about Company products and services, changes to the Website, promotional updates, and special offers.

We use cookies, which are small pieces of text stored on your computer, to provide services that are tailored to you. We track certain information about you (such as your IP address, your browser type, and the URLs that you came from and go to next) based on your activity on the Company Website. We use this information to provide personalized advertisements on other Websites, to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Website, and to gather broad demographic information. We may also use your personal information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, to improve our content offerings, and to customize our Website's services. Company never uses cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent or stored in a cookie.

* * *

**Disclosure of Information To Outside Parties**

From time to time, Company may share information with outside parties. For example, Company sometimes engages other companies and individuals to perform functions on its behalf such as fulfilling orders and delivering packages, among other things. Those other companies have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes and do not have access to your credit card or other payment information. 

Additionally, we may provide aggregate statistics about Web site users, traffic patterns, and related site information to third parties. Company may also release information when we believe that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with a subpoena, Court order, or legal process, (ii) enforce or comply with the provisions of the Terms and Conditions or other Agreement with Company; and (iii) protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our users, or others. 

We use cookies, which are small pieces of text stored on your computer, to provide services that are tailored to you. We track certain information about you (such as your IP address, your browser type, and the URLs that you came from and go to next) based on your activity on the Company Website. We use this information to provide personalized advertisements on other Websites, to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Website, and to gather broad demographic information. We may also use your personal information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, to improve our content offerings, and to customize our Website's services. Company never uses cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent or stored in a cookie.

Unfortunately, due to the existing regulatory and Internet environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will remain absolutely private.

* * *

**Children's Privacy**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. You should be aware that this site is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.

* * *

**Security**

Company uses Secured Sockets Layer technology to ensure the privacy of your personal information. When you provide us with information, our advanced security technology encrypts or scrambles your personal data (including your name, e-mail addresses, and credit card number) before it is sent to us, making it virtually impossible for anyone other than Company to read it. To further protect your information, we utilize state of the art back-end systems and restrict employee access to your information. Unless specifically authorized by Company, no outside party is able to access or receive any personal customer information.

* * *

**Links**

This site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our site. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those other sites and you should evaluate their practices before deciding to view their site or use their services.

* * *

**Changing, Correcting, or Removing Your Information**

For changes, corrections, or deletions to your personal information from our database, please contact Customer Service at service@positivepromotions.com.

We will retain in our files information that you have requested to remove in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our Terms and Conditions. Further, such prior information will never be completely removed from our databases due to technical constraints and the fact that we back up our systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

* * *

**Contacting Company**

If you have any questions about Company's Privacy Policy or practices, you can contact us at service@positivepromotions.com.

Additionally, we may provide aggregate statistics about Web site users, traffic patterns, and related site information to third parties. Company may also release information when we believe that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with a subpoena, Court order, or legal process, (ii) enforce or comply with the provisions of the Terms and Conditions or other Agreement with Company; and (iii) protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our users, or others.

* * *

**Changes to This Policy**

Company reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, effective immediately upon the posting on this site. Please check this page of the site periodically. Your continued use of the Company Website indicates your consent to the changed or amended terms of this Privacy Policy.

* * *
